A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Politics - New York City Office, Series J.1 FA345
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Polls, 1958-1970; 4; 6 Document Box(es)
  - National Media Analysis Reports - Reports 31-35, 37-40, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 719)
  - National Media Analysis Reports - Reports 41-44. 48-49, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 720)
  - "New York State Opinion: Potential Candidates for U.S. Senator", February 1970 (Box 66, Folder 721)
  - "Political Opinion in New York State", April-May 1970 (Box 66, Folder 722)
  - "Political Opinion in New York State", April-May 1970 (Box 66, Folder 723)
  - "Poll Data about Gubernatorial Candidates", July-August 1970 (Box 67, Folder 724)
  - "Poll Data about Gubernatorial Candidates", July-August 1970 (Box 67, Folder 725)
  - "Public Attitudes Affecting the Rockefeller Candidacy", September 1970 (Box 67, Folder 726)
  - "The Senatorial Race in New York State", September-October 1970 (Box 67, Folder 0726A)
  - "Standing of Gubernatorial Candidates", September 1970 (Box 67, Folder 727)
  - "Subway Survey", August 1970 (Box 67, Folder 728)
  - Telephone Check of Lindsay Popularity, March 1970 (Box 67, Folder 729)
- Office of the Governor, 1958-1971; 5; 14 Document Box(es)
  Subseries 5 is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  This subseries, a collection of alphabetically arranged subject files, partially documents the early years of Rockefeller's tenure as Governor. The majority of the files dates from Governor Rockefeller's inauguration in January 1959 or document activities in the first two administrations. A few files date as late as 1971. Few files offer complete documentation of a particular issue or activity.
  - 55th Street Headquarters (Box 67, Folder 730)
    List of individuals telephone extensions at 22 W. 55th Street.
  - Archives, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 731)
    1964 memo from Rockefeller Family Archivist Joseph W. Ernst on how best to deal with the disposition of NAR's papers.
  - Articles about NAR, 1959-1970 (Box 67, Folder 732)
    NAR Message to Legislature January 1960; Metropolitan Area Problems March/April 1961; Message to Legislature January 1964; "Thus We Are Yankees" by E. Lumsden - Rockefellers in Politics; "Rockefeller Has To Win" "New York Times Magazine" May 9, 1965; Washington Square Press request to NAR to write preface to book about New York State, October 1962; Memos (1959) re "Life Magazine" series, family pictures; magazine article on family.
  - Attica, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 733)
    Public comment on Attica prison riot; press release September 16, 1971; copy of Duke University "Chronicle," September 27, 1971; Jewish Defense League statement re exchange of Attica inmates for Soviet Jews.
  - Attica, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 734)
  - Certificates of Election and Inauguration, 1962-1970 (Box 67, Folder 735)
  - Clippings, 1959-1971 (Box 68, Folder 736)
    Clippings re NAR inauguration, inaugural address & fiscal policies.
  - Committee on Scholastic Achievement, 1967-1971 (Box 68, Folder 737)
    NAR contributions to the committee.
  - Conference on Automation, June 1960 (Box 68, Folder 738)
    Report by Eli Ginzberg, "Automation and Manpower."
  - Conference on Natural Beauty, February 1966 (Box 68, Folder 739)
    Memos on conference at New York Hilton.
  - Conference on Oceanography, July 1967 (Box 68, Folder 740)
    NAR announcement on conference; Dr. Detlev Bronk, President of Rockefeller University, to serve as director of conference.
  - Correspondence - Appeals, 1959-1970 (Box 68, Folder 741)
    Miscellaneous appeals.
  - Correspondence - Applications - Lists, 1959-1970 (Box 68, Folder 742)
    Applications filed for positions, resumes.
  - Correspondence - Appointment Requests, 1959-1970 (Box 68, Folder 743)
    Requests for appointments with NAR.
  - Correspondence - Appreciation Letters, 1959-1970 (Box 68, Folder 744)
    Letters of appreciation to NAR for his kindness.
  - Correspondence - Appreciation Letters to Appointees, 1958-1959 (Box 68, Folder 745)
    Letters of appreciation to key NAR associates & staff.
  - Correspondence - Appreciation Letters to Family, 1958-1959 (Box 68, Folder 746)
  - Correspondence - Appreciation Letters to Family, 1958-1959 (Box 68, Folder 0746A)
  - Correspondence - Congratulatory Letters on 1962 Election (Box 68, Folder 747)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (A), 1959-1970 (Box 68, Folder 748)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (B), 1959-1970 (Box 68, Folder 749)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (C), 1959-1970 (Box 68, Folder 750)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (D), 1959-1970 (Box 69, Folder 751)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (E), 1959-1970 (Box 69, Folder 752)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (F), 1959-1970 (Box 69, Folder 753)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (G), 1959-1970 (Box 69, Folder 754)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (H), 1959-1970 (Box 69, Folder 755)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (I-J), 1959-1970 (Box 69, Folder 756)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (K-L), 1959-1970 (Box 69, Folder 757)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (M), 1959-1970 (Box 69, Folder 758)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (N-O), 1959-1970 (Box 69, Folder 759)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (P-Q), 1959-1970 (Box 69, Folder 760)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (R), 1959-1970 (Box 69, Folder 761)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (S), 1959-1970 (Box 69, Folder 762)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (T), 1959-1970 (Box 70, Folder 763)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (U-W), 1959-1970 (Box 70, Folder 764)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (X-Z), 1959-1970 (Box 70, Folder 765)
  - Courtesy Calls - Memos & Correspondence, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 766)
    NAR courtesy calls to foreign dignitaries.
  - Danzig, Jerry, 1962-1963 (Box 70, Folder 767)
    1963 letter to NAR re his wedding; TV & radio coverage & appearances.
  - DNA (Definitive News Analysis) Research, 1959-1968 (Box 70, Folder 768)
    Definitive News Analysis (DNA) research personnel list; January 1961 memo by R. Perkins to NAR re material available in research section; management and personnel issues, effectiveness of DNA research.
  - Discussions, Speeches, etc., 1958-1961 (Box 70, Folder 769)
    Press releases of addresses & discussions; some NAR texts; clippings; NAR off-the-record discussion with press regarding nuclear weapons & fallout shelters.
  - Emancipation Proclamation 100th Anniversary, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 770)
    Memos re celebration of 100th anniversary September 1962.
  - Entertainment, 1959-1962 (Box 70, Folder 771)
    Memos re receptions & luncheons; State Defense Council luncheon July 1959.
  - Executive Chamber, 1959-1965 (Box 70, Folder 772)
    Gov. A. E. Smith State Office Building; State Campus Telephone Directory; September 1959 added budget for publications; organizations & functions of Executive Chamber June 1959.
  - Expense Accounts, 1959-1971 (Box 70, Folder 773)
    Payments from petty cash; IRS letter of March 1965 re expense allowances for Governor; authorizations for miscellaneous payments.
  - Fact Sheet - New York State/New York City Fiscal Relations, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 774)
    H. O'Donnell on New York State & New York City fiscal relationship.
  - Foreign Visitors, 1959-1970 (Box 71, Folder 775)
    Department of State for the Press - announcements of foreign visitors; miscellaneous memos re foreign visitors; miscellaneous memos of visits of foreign dignitaries; information for use during visit of Nikita S. Khrushchev September 1959.
  - Foreign Visitors, 1959-1970 (Box 71, Folder 776)
  - Foreign Visitors, 1959-1970 (Box 71, Folder 777)
  - Foreign Visitors, 1959-1970 (Box 71, Folder 778)
  - Foreign Visitors - de Gaulle, Charles, President of France, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 779)
    Toast for de Gaulle; miscellaneous information for use during visit.
  - Foreign Visitors - Toure, Sekou, President of Guinea, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 780)
    Program for visit; tentative list of members of part for the visit; background material on New Guinea & members of party; visit to Museum of Primitive Art.
  - Foreign Visitors - United Nations Delegates, 1959-1970 (Box 71, Folder 781)
    Meeting, May 1961 at U.S. mission to United Nations; memos re assurance of friendly & dignified treatment for representatives of foreign countries.
  - Friele, Berent, 1959-1964 (Box 71, Folder 782)
    Miscellaneous memos & correspondence.
  - General Correspondence & Memos, 1962-1971 (Box 71, Folder 783)
    Clippings re 1965 inauguration, cleaning State Capitol & NAR's 55th St. office; memo re NAR's papers May 1964; old picture book of State Capitol; congratulations, 1962.
  - Gifts - Accepted, 1959-1969 (Box 71, Folder 784)
    NAR's letters of acceptance for gifts.
  - Gifts - Returned, 1959-1970 (Box 72, Folder 785)
    NAR letters of declination as to policy re non-acceptance of gifts except from family members or close friends; letters concern primarily return of portraits & art works.
  - Gifts - Returned, 1959-1970 (Box 72, Folder 786)
  - Gifts - Returned, 1959-1970 (Box 72, Folder 787)
  - Harris, Mary (McCann-Erickson), 1959 (Box 72, Folder 788)
    McCann-Erickson campaign advertising; Mary Harris correspondence.
  - Honorary Positions, Memberships, Sponsorships, Awards, 1958-1959 (Box 72, Folder 789)
    Honorary positions, and awards offered to NAR; replies.
  - Housing - New York City, 1961-1964 (Box 72, Folder 790)
    May 1964 report to NAR suggesting a new approach to urban design & "New City" neighborhood center for lower Manhattan, by Harrison & Abramowitz; November 1961, Space for Urban Living.
  - Housing - New York City - Task Force on Middle Income Housing, 1958-1961 (Box 72, Folder 791)
    1959 report on middle-income housing; related memos.
  - Hudson - Champlain Celebration, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 792)
    Visit by Princess Beatrix of Netherlands, background, party, telegram; meeting of New York City Department of Commerce August 1959; New York State Year of History, 350th Anniversary Hudson-Champlain Celebration, 1609-1959 - booklet; Temporary State Commission on Historic Observances.
  - Hudson - Champlain Celebration, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 793)
  - Hudson - Champlain Celebration, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 794)
  - Hughes, Emmet J., 1959-1962 (Box 73, Folder 795)
    "Political Labels Are Nonsense," "Saturday Eveing Post," 1962; October 1959 suggestions for dealing with Soviet Union; November 1961 NAR statement re issue of resumed nuclear testing; 1962 Inaugural, Opening, Closing Messages and Adderss; miscellaneous speeches.
  - Inauguration, 1959 - Inauguration, 1958-1959 (Box 73, Folder 796)
    Summary of "New York Times" accounts of inaugural ceremonies for Governors Harriman and Dewey, their addresses; NAR address 1959; schedule of ceremony; photos of Dewey inauguration.
  - Inauguration, 1959 - Inaugurations - Previous, 1943, 1951, 1955 (Box 73, Folder 797)
    Schedules, press releases, arrangements, organization.
  - Inauguration, 1959 - Address - Background Material, 1943-1955 (Box 73, Folder 798)
    Background on addresses & inaugurations of Governors Dewey & Harriman.
  - Inauguration, 1959 - Ceremony, 1958-1959 (Box 74, Folder 799)
    Invitations to inaugural ceremony & ball; guest lists; suggested procedures for large dinner; arrangements made; Goeller memo re procedures 11/24/57 & list of contributors, 1958; thank you letters re decorations & family Bible.
  - Inauguration, 1959 - Ceremony (Box 74, Folder 800)
  - Inauguration, 1959 - Correspondence (Box 74, Folder 801)
    Invitations to inaugural ceremony & ball; swearing-in; acceptances & regrets; clippings; congratulations.
  - Inauguration, 1959 - Dinner, December 31, 1958 & Swearing-in Party (Box 74, Folder 802)
    Guest lists & invitations.
  - Inauguration, 1959 - Inaugural Ball, January 1, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 803)
    Invitation list; arrangements made; sample invitation; tentative program.
  - Inauguration, 1959 - Inauguration Ticket Requests (Box 74, Folder 804)
    Requests for tickets to attend inaugural ceremonies.
  - Inauguration, 1963 (Box 74, Folder 805)
    NAR schedule; invitations to NAR's children; organization chart & diagram of seating arrangements; plans for reception & open house; Inaugural Prayer; invitation list for Swearing-In Ceremony; copy of NAR address.
  - Inauguration, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 806)
    Address lists for invitations; press releases re Inauguration Ceremony & open house; Inaugural Ball; booklet re inauguration & invitation; luncheon; press release of NAR address.
  - Inauguration, 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 74, Folder 807)
    Plans for Inauguration Ceremony & open house; 12/18/70 press release re ceremonies; excerpts from 1/1/71 address; NAR oath of office; 1/6/71 clipping re state of the state message to legislature.
  - Invitations & Invitations to Speak, 1959-1962 (Box 74, Folder 808)
    Miscellaneous invitations re dinners, memberships, etc.; invitations to speak.
  - Invitations & Invitations to Speak, 1959-1962 (Box 74, Folder 809)
  - Jones, Nina, 1968-1971 (Box 75, Folder 810)
    NAR's personal representative in Westchester; background on Village elections March 1971; Hudson River Expressway, excerpts from Subcommittee on Fisheries & Wildlife; Westchester 1968 pre-election report; miscellaneous memos re Westchester County.
  - Jones, Nina, 1968-1971 (Box 75, Folder 811)
  - Labor, 1959-1968 (Box 75, Folder 812)
    New York City strike by sanitation men, March 1968; NAR relationship with William Green & Philip Murray, March 1963; New York State Motion Picture Theater Owners Minimum Wage Committee.
  - Legislation, 1959-1960 (Box 75, Folder 813)
    Federal grants for sewage treatment works May 1959; NAR message re Statutory Minimum Wage, higher benefits urged January 1960.
  - Lists, 1959 (Box 75, Folder 814)
    State Department heads, addresses & phone numbers.
  - Losee, Thomas, 1959 (Box 75, Folder 815)
    Public Relations Group Meetings, etc.; October 1959 memo to Stephen David re background information on International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) & Rockefeller Brothers, Inc.; December 1959 - literature - reprints of magazine articles on NAR.
  - Mansion - General, 1960-1971 (Box 75, Folder 816)
    Booklets re mansion; landscaping & interior decorating; blueprints; china service in use; furniture for porch; executive mansion schedules 1966, 1968, 1969, 1971.
  - Mansion - Fire, March 1961 (Box 75, Folder 817)
    Clippings; damage to works of art; paintings offered to NAR; list of personal items damaged; report on fire.
  - Mansion - Gifts to New York State (Box 75, Folder 818)
    NAR gifts of antique furniture and framed prints.
  - Mansion - Pool House, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 819)
    Photographs of china; purchase of Spode china; inventory of stainless flatware for Bath House; fabric samples.
  - Mansion - Requests to See, 1959-1965 (Box 75, Folder 820)
    Requests to see art collection at mansion.
  - Mansion - Staff Memos, 1959-1967 (Box 75, Folder 821)
    Budget & staff memos; household expenses; miscellaneous bills.
  - Mansion - Tennis Courts, 1959-1967 (Box 75, Folder 822)
    Construction & maintenance.
  - May, Stacy, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 823)
    Memo to NAR re Mrs. Roosevelt; 1960 panel discussion article from "World Telegram Sun"; 1960 comment on Fidal Castro.
  - McManus, Robert L., 1959-1960 (Box 76, Folder 824)
    Editorial comment on reapportionment, post-election comment on national matters & state matters, comment on Nixon-Rockefeller exchange; mailing list for NAR's article "Purpose & Policy" in April 1960 issue of "Foreign Affairs"; excerpts of NAR remarks at annual Pan American Day luncheon, April 1960.
  - Medallic Art Company, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 825)
    Correspondence & memos re World's Fair medallions; orders.
  - Memos, Reminders, Appointments, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 826)
    Schedules for meals with dignitaries.
  - Message to the Legislature - Annual Message, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 827)
  - Message to the Legislature - Annual Message, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 828)
  - Message to the Legislature - Budget Message, 1958-1960 (Box 76, Folder 829)
  - Message to the Legislature - Budget Message, 1964-1965 (Box 76, Folder 830)
  - Message to the Legislature - Budget Message, 1965-1966 (Box 76, Folder 831)
  - Message to the Legislature - Budget Message, 1966-1967 (Box 76, Folder 832)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 1960-1970 (Box 76, Folder 833)
    Excerpts of NAR remarks, September 1970; photo of NAR at opening of Robert Motherwell show at Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), September 1964; members of council in 1961; Touring Program 1968-1969; NAR's "Good Art Is Good Business & Good Politics," October 1967.
  - New York State Council On the Arts - Annual Reports, 1966-1970 (Box 76, Folder 834)
  - Perkins, Roswell B., 1959-1963 (Box 76, Folder 835)
    Amendments to King-Anderson bill; permanent records of program materials (Pre-campaign, Campaign &1959 Legislative Session).
  - Phone Calls Record, 1958-1959 (Box 76, Folder 836)
    Record of calls made by NAR.
  - Polls, 1959 (Box 77, Folder 837)
    NAR Albany polls - ratings; ratings on NAR's broadcasts of February 1959; "New York Daily News" polls.
  - Press Comments & Cartoons, 1958-1960 (Box 77, Folder 838)
    Clippings about NAR.
  - Press Conference Transcripts, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 839)
    Transcript of NAR press conference in Albany, February 1961.
  - Procedures and Staff Memos, 1958-1964 (Box 77, Folder 840)
  - Proclamations, 1966-1967 (Box 77, Folder 841)
    Proclamations re Pan American Day & Pan American Week April 1967.
  - Publicity, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 842)
    Copies of letters of appreciation from Franklin D. Roosevelt (1945) for NAR's service as Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs and Harry Truman (1951) for service as chairman of International Development Advisory Board. Summary of state and federal government roles of NAR July 1958; letter (1958) from Herbert H. Lehman re NAR's speech at Am. Jewish Committee dinner. Campaign pamphlets.
  - Puerto Rico, 1958-1960 (Box 77, Folder 843)
    Puerto Rican appointments; articles of recognition of NAR.
  - Purchases, Tickets, Reservations, etc., 1959 (Box 77, Folder 844)
    Tickets for Johansson-Patterson fight 6/25/59 at Yankee Stadium; thank you note for ticket from Mrs. John Davison Rockefeller 3rd's chauffeur.
  - Radio - Television, 1959-1967 (Box 77, Folder 845)
    April 1967 invitation for NAR to appear on David Susskind Show; May 1959 bills in connection with NAR's TV appearances; memos concerning NAR appearances, etc.
  - Radio - Television Programs - Bernard Fitler Memos, 1960 (Box 77, Folder 846)
    TV programs, education; civil defense film "Survival or Suicide;" Broadcasting - Legislative Series.
  - Reports - Annual Report, New York State Racing Association, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 847)
  - Reports - Annual Report of the Superintendent of Banks, 1959 (Box 77, Folder 848)
  - Reports - New York Report, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 849)
  - Reports - "Proposed Reorganization of the Executive Branch of New York State", 1959 (Box 77, Folder 850)
  - Reports - Special Legislative Committee on Revision & Simplification of New York State Constitution, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 851)
  - Reports - Special Task Force on Protection Against Radioactive Fallout, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 852)
  - Reports - Special Task Force on Protection Against Radioactive Fallout, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 853)
  - Reports - Special Task Force on Protection Against Radioactive Fallout, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 854)
  - Resignations, 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 855)
    NAR resignations from boards & committees upon becoming Governor.
  - Root, Oren, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 856)
    Correspondence of Oren Root, responsible for processing invitations & requests for NAR's personal appearances.
  - St. Lawrence Seaway, 1958-1960 (Box 79, Folder 857)
    Photographs; report by Power Authority of New York, data, statistics, maps & diagrams, February 1958; July 1958 President Eisenhower inspects seaway power projects.
  - Savell, Isabelle K., 1958-1964 (Box 79, Folder 858)
    Reimbursement for book purchases, "New York Post Daily" magazine article, May 1963.
  - Schedules, 1958-1970 (Box 79, Folder 859)
    Miscellaneous schedules for NAR - personal & Executive Mansion.
  - South Mall Development, 1966-1969 (Box 79, Folder 860)
    Sculptor Marcelo Bonevardi bio; general correspondence.
  - Speech, April 22, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 861)
    "The Third Century," A Concept of American Foreign Policy.
  - Staff & Staff Memos, 1961-1967 (Box 79, Folder 862)
    1965 list of 55th St. personnel; 1961 list of names and addresses of heads of New York State Departments; miscellaneous memoranda 1961-1967.
  - Studies, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 863)
    Checklist of studies & other matters requiring follow-up culled from messages & statements made by NAR; special studies to be undertaken.
  - Transportation, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 864)
    1959 special report to NAR on problems of the railroad and bus lines in New York State.
  - Trip, Massachusetts, February 1962 (Box 79, Folder 865)
    Brief summary of outstanding state issues in Massachusetts.
  - United Nations Delegates Visit to Albany, October 1959 (Box 79, Folder 866)
    Statement by Senator Hatfield, chairman of New York State Commission on Historic Observances re proposed visit to Albany by United Nations delegates; list of guests invited; trip canceled due to delegates' heavy schedule.
  - Welfare (Box 79, Folder 867)
    Memos & reports - New York State Citizens Committee on Costs, 1965.
  - Wilson, Malcolm, 1964-1968 (Box 79, Folder 868)
    Correspondence with NAR; memos; NAR gift to Wilson of painting "Father of His Country" by Howard Chandler Christie.
  - Women's Unit in Office of Secretary to Governor, 1967-1969 (Box 80, Folder 869)
    Background information on members of Westchester Council of Social Agencies, Inc., 1967; statement by G. Newlin, pres. of Council for the Arts in Westchester; list of names for Transportation Committee, 1967; Women's Unit literature, personnel & activity reports.
  - Women's Unit in Office of Secretary to Governor, 1967-1969 (Box 80, Folder 870)
  - Women's Unit in Office of Secretary to Governor, 1967-1969 (Box 80, Folder 871)
  - Women's Unit - Representative Samples, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 872)
    Miscellaneous memos & reports.
  - Women's Unit - Representative Samples, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 873)
  - Women's Unit - Representative Samples, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 874)
  - World's Fair, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 875)
    Operation Sail.
  - Magazines Featuring NAR - Look, "A Rockefeller Runs for Governor", October 14, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 876)
    p. 73
  - Magazines Featuring NAR - Look, "Battle of the Millionaires", October 25, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 877)
    p. 38
  - Magazines Featuring NAR - New York News Magazine, "They're Off -- and Running for Office", November 2, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 878)
    p. 15
  - Magazines Featuring NAR - Life, August 11, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 879)
    Photo of NAR in article on photograph, p. 2.
  - Magazines Featuring NAR - Life, "A Voter's Choice of Millionaires", September 22, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 880)
    p. 104
  - Magazines Featuring NAR - Newsweek, "The Millionaires -- Which? The Thin Edge", November 3, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 881)
    p. 30 [NAR on cover]
  - Magazines Featuring NAR - The New Yorker, "Candidates", October 4, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 882)
    p. 34
  - Magazines Featuring NAR - The Reporter, "Can Rockefeller Save the GOP in New York", October 30, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 883)
    p. 9
  - Magazines Featuring NAR - Time, "The Rocky Roll", October 6, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 884)
    p. 16; see also editor's note on p. 11; [NAR on cover]
  - Magazines Featuring NAR - Sports Illustrated, "A Racing Rockefeller", August 4, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 885)
    p. 26
  - Magazines Featuring NAR - The Nelson Rockefeller Story, 2 copies (Box 81, Folder 886)